iccu.com 2016-11-06

# 

                                                                                                           Rev. October 2010
                      WHAT DOES IDAHO CENTRAL CREDIT UNION DO
FACTS                 WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
                      Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives
Why?                  consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how
                      we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to
                      understand what we do.
What?                 The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you
                      have with us. This information can include:
                            Social Security number and checking account information
                            account balances and payment history
                            credit history and credit scores
                      When you are no longer our member, we continue to share your information as described in this
                      notice.
How?                  All financial companies need to share members' personal information to run their everyday
                      business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their members'
                      personal information; the reasons Idaho Central Credit Union chooses to share; and whether you
                      can limit this sharing.
                                                              Does Idaho Central Credit
Reasons we can share your personal information                                              Can you limit this sharing?
                                                                    Union share?
For our everyday business purposes—
such as to process your transactions, maintain
                                                                        Yes                              No
your account(s), respond to court orders and legal
investigations, or report to credit bureaus
For our marketing purposes—
                                                                        Yes                              No
to offer our products and services to you
For joint marketing with other financial companies                      Yes                             Yes
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—
                                                                         No                       We don't share
information about your transactions and experiences
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—
                                                                         No                       We don't share
information about your creditworthiness
For non-affiliates to market to you                                     Yes                             Yes
Questions?            Call 800-456-5067 or go to www.iccu.com

Page 2
What we do
How does Idaho Central Credit Union To protect your personal information from unauthorized access
protect my personal information?    and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law.
                                    These measures include computer safeguards and secured files
                                    and buildings.
How does Idaho Central Credit Union We collect your personal information, for example, when you
collect my personal information?        open an account or deposit money
                                        pay your bills or apply for a loan
                                        use your debit card
                                    We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit
                                    bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?      Federal law gives you the right to limit only
                                        sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information
                                         about your creditworthiness
                                        affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                        sharing for non-affiliates to market to you
                                    State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to
                                    limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates                          Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                    financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                        Idaho Central Credit Union has no affiliates
Non-affiliates                      Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                    financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                        Non-affiliates we share with can include government entities,
                                         credit bureaus, and insurance companies.
Joint marketing                     A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that
                                    together market financial products or services to you.
                                        Our joint marketing partners include insurance companies.
